mazarscareers.ie 2017-11-14

# Mazars CareersMazars Careers

This privacy policy sets out how Mazars uses and protects any information that you give Mazars when you use this website.

Mazars is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected in line with the requirements of the Data Protection Policy 1988- 2003. Should you provide information by which you can be identified, when using this website, then the information will only be used in accordance with this data protection & privacy statement.

Mazars may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 17th September 2012.

#### What we collect

We collect the following information including: 

Personal details such as - 
  * Name and contact details
  * Educational background
  * Interests/hobbies
  * Work experience

#### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to process your application for the Graduate Recruitment Programme 2013.

#### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

#### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

#### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

#### Controlling your personal information and Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. 

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Human Resources Department, Mazars, Harcourt Centre, Block 3, Harcourt Road, Dublin 2 or email hello@mazarscareers.ie or you can print a copy of your application form on the website

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
